there was this video that came out of
this guy this single hiker who was being
chased or like stalked by a mountain
lion for like a good five to ten minutes
okay and I want you to know it's one of
my favorite stories in the world my
friend was so excited to tell me he was
like Jordan I don't know if you've seen
this video it's a video it's a hiker
he's being stalked by a mountain lion
for like five to ten minutes he's hiking
by himself he's a white guy I was like
you didn't have to tell me he was white
I knew it
you said lone hiker that spell that
backwards it spells white guy I'm
letting you know
there's no there's no way you're gonna
tell black people don't hike by
themselves and when we do we're going to
7-Eleven to buy Hot Cheetos like I'm
that's what it is matter of fact the
last time I went hiking by myself I went
with my Men's Choir for a church retreat
but it was too many black people that
were really afraid to hike so we went to
our local park and sat in the sandbox
for 72 hours next to phone chargers
because there's
black people need reception when we hike
the minute a black person you got a
reception you got nope let's go lock it
up let's go back
we're good we're good
there's no way I'm just it's insane to
me like it trips me out like me myself
like it's not I'm joking obviously like
I hike you know what I mean like my
Heights are just normally shorter than
everyone else's like I hike from my car
to the sign that tells you what
dangerous animals you might encounter I
read it I hike back that's it
that is it now my favorite thing about
like the story about the mountain lion
versus the hiker I just learned that
that happened here
when I found that out I was like oh so
duh because like every black person I
see in Utah I'm like you don't belong
here I don't know what's happening
like that person at Zion I looked at him
deadly eye and whispered are you
like I don't
I want you to know every black person
that I've encountered you everyone else
and all the white people are so nice
you're like hi good morning but when I
see a black person he don't even make
eye contact I'm like somebody needs to
flash a camera in his face right now
[Applause]
I don't know I'm so sorry that was a
personal story um
[Applause]
is
the reason why I don't hike by myself is
because like I feel like you need a
safety net so I need to go with a
partner and the reason being is because
if we encounter Reliant we can't get
away but I can so uh
I just realized I said safety net I
meant to say sacrifice and that was my
fault that was my fault
that was my bad because I'm gonna do it
in all situations it doesn't matter if
I'm in like if I'm hiking or if I'm in
the streets I'm I'm not gonna be that
tough guy okay like I could be with my
lady okay and if a guy walks up six feet
tall super huge guy if he walks up to me
and he's like hey is that your girl I'm
like hey not if you want her sir not if
[Applause]
not if you want to because Jesus said
ask and ye shall receive so I'm
asking if you take her I receive another
girl in Jesus name Hallelujah like that
[Applause]
that's who I am as a person there's no
way around it I'm going to figure it out
I'm not tough you can tell by my voice I
won't win a threatening competition okay
this guy told me I sound like Katt
Williams but I look like I would name my
cat Williams I was like I was like his
name is Oliver um I have two cats um
it's insane I like I will do whatever I
can to get out of a fighting situation
and fun fact if you don't know what it
takes to get out of a fight when someone
tries to threaten you just play dumb and
take whatever they say literally you'll
get out of the fight all the time I do
it all the time you want a piece of me
I'm not hungry I'm not I'm not hungry at
all matter of fact I just ate if I eat a
gim that's gonna lead to high blood
pressure that's big in the black
community so I don't want to keep that
stereotype going so I'm good
well you could just kiss my butt not
without chapstick sir my lips are
currently dry so
if I kiss it now it's gonna make your
butt bleed I just want you to know our
next if you got it I'll take it but
you trying to go I never called an Uber
sir I don't know where you think I'm
trying to go but it's not with you
matter of fact it's Saturday night it's
late if I'm going anywhere I'm going
home to get my rest because I gotta wake
up and Praise Jesus with a line of
energy so it'll get you out every time
hi
I was Jordan Conley I was the comedian
and I want to thank you so much and I'm
going to thank you again because you're
amazing also make sure you download the
drive our comedy app okay it's an
amazing app and guess who's on it I am
my name is Jordan Conley thank you for
watching but number three do you want to
hear something amazing come closer come
closer oh wait cameraman said he's not
going to zoom in use the code Jordan
Conley and you're going to be amazed
yeah bye-bye now